Tufts Observer UP055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Observer, 1994 -- 1996; UP055.024; 1.2 Linear Feet
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-02-08; UP055.024.024.00045 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Elizabeth] Ammons Resignation Announced. Former French President [Valery] Giscard d'Estaing Graces Cohen Tonight. TCU [Tufts Community Union] Senate Votes No Culture Rep. Tufts Community Questions Writing Aptitude of Students. Lifeline, Cityline, Waiting for Green Light. The 'Quinto'ssential Math Lover. Bowling for Cash Prizes, National Ranking. Greek Life Avoids Mishap; Rush Ambiguity Continues. Board of Trustees to Hold Annual Meeting Today. 'Songs' [Gospel Concert] Celebrates Life, History. [Coach Bob] Sheldon Now Tops at Tufts. Tufts' [Hockey] Winning Streak Ends at Six Games. Men's Track Triumphs With Tough Training. Men's Squash Fights Frustration, Futility. Women's Hoops Still Singing the Blues. Finally Six-ess: Men's Hoops Meets Expectations. [Justin] Rishel Carries The Torch [For Hockey Team]. Swimmers Hum Final Tune (Up).
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-02-15; UP055.024.024.00046 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Senate Grapples With Culture Reps. Trustees Appoint Two Deans [Lonnie H. Morris, Philip C. Kosch]. French President d'Estaing Lecture on the Middle East. Annual Luncheon Highlighted By financial Woes. The Man Behind The Aura of No. 22 [Chad Onofrio]. The Most Exciting Sox This Side of Fenway. Tufts the Place for Change During the '60s. Administration Reflects On [Elizabeth] Ammons' Two Years As Dean. Holly Sklar Speaks About 'The Dying American Dream'. Technology Moves To Head Of Class. Lavalle Leads the TCUJ [Tufts Community Union Judiciary] Down The Path of Justice. Women's Hoops Behind the Eight Ball. Women's Swimmers Finish on a High Note. Williams Turns Tufts [Men's Basketball] Inside Out. Jumbos [Squash] Hyped For Howe [Cup.] Men's Squash Peaks in Time For Nationals. Jumbos [Hockey] Pounds Panthers. Women's Track Gets One Last Warm Up. Sometimes Nothing Matters [For Hockey]. [Men's] Hoops Has Hopes For NCAA [National Collegiate Athletic Association] Bid. Rams Not Tough Enough For Jumbos [Hockey]. No Clowning Around for [Men's] Hoops. Men's Track Prepares for Ephmen's Onslaught.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-02-22; UP055.024.024.00047 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Media Studies Announces New Minor. Med Dean Search Complicated By Hospital Merger. Postering Policy's Problems Persist. CFS [Committee on fraternities and sororities] to Try It Again, Without Faculty Members. Senate Puts Money on Success Of Casino Night. It's None of Our Business [Major]. Senior [Gregory Gertner] Swims In Alphabet Soup. Fencers Lunge Toward New England Win. University Tries To bring Alcohol to Campus. 'Henry' Fights His Way to Balch Arena Theater. Women's Hoops An Imperfect 10. Women's Swimming Shifts Into High Gear. Tufts [Hockey] Seeks Perfect Playoff Recipe. [Chad] Onofrio On His Game. 'Howe' [Cup] Great: Women's Squash Finishes Hot. [Justin] Rishel, Jumbos Dealt Season- Ending Blow. Bus Company Denies Women's Track Team. Men's Track Breathes Second Wind at New England Champs. Jumbos [men'sbasketball] Fall Flat in Fourth Quarter Test. Men's Hoops Blow 12-point lead To Amherst.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-02-29; UP055.024.024.00048 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Sonny's Rollin' Into Tufts. [Arthur] Sulzberger Jr. Shines With Alumni Award. Lack of Support Sends Culture Forum Back to the Drawing Board. Two UNICCO [University Cleaning Company] Employees Sexually Harassed on Campus. Dining Services Envisions Pound as Future Carry out Facility for Hurried Students. [Courtney, a] Junior Has Sound 'Reed' of Politics. Tempers Flare For ACT [Asian Community at Tufts], ALBO [Allocations Board] at Sunday's Senate Meeting. Campus Social Life in State of Flux. Two-Dean System at Turning Point. 'Henry' offers an Innovative Take on Shakespeare. Womens' Hoops Misery Ends. Men's Squash Enjoys Happy Ending. Women's Swim Team Enjoys Revenge. Not a Fond Farewell For [Basketball] Seniors. Men's Swimming gets Back for New Englands. A Not So Special Loss [ice hockey]. Jumbos [hockey] Can't Take Out the Trash. [men's basketball] Defense Falters in 88-85 Loss at UMASS-Dartmouth. Curtain Falls on Hockey Team in ECAC [Eastern College Athletic Conference] tourney. New Englands Productive for Track: It's Lucky 13 For Men's Team; Women Place 14th at Bowdoin.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-03-07; UP055.024.024.00049 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Israel Bombings Touch Tufts Community. Time to Play Ball! [Gym Construction Completed]. Library Collection Woes Persist Despite Many Improvement Efforts. TUTV [Tufts University Television] Closes on Cable Role. Vacated Jackson Space Possibly To Be Converted to Arts Performance Area. Harvard Envy: How do Tufts Students Compare to Peers at Rival Universities?. Say 'Chai' To Hillel President [Sarah Oller]. Serving Catholic Students' Spiritual Needs. Senator [John] Kerry to Highlight 18th Annual New England Environmental Conference. Women's Track 19th; [Rachel] Wildman Leads Pack. Women's Forum Moved To Cabot [Auditorium]. Spring is in the Air: Softballs, Baseball, Lacrosse Teams Hit the Road for Spring. National Treasures: [Laurie] Katz, [Jenna] Postar, [Jen] Ward Seeking Fortune at Diving Finals. Tufts [Men's] Track Angles Into 2nd at ECACs. Seniors' [Swimming] Strength Sparks Jumbos.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-03-28; UP055.024.024.00050 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. P-Funk and Femmes to Thrill the Hill. Takeout Food at Hodgdon Next Semester. Tufts Evaluates Responsibility in UNICCO [University Cleaning Company] Matters. [Ancy] Verdier Named Wendell Phillips Award Winner. Forum to Investigate Taiwan and China's Relationship. Constitution Approaches Vote. Living By the Power of Humor [Seymour Simches.] Aloha State Culture Flowering on Hill. Protest, Mayhem, Theft Shatter Serenity of Tufts in '68. Congressman [Henry] Waxman Speaks on Health Care. CSL [Committee on Student Life] Regroups Near The Semester's End. Men's Track Wants More of the Same. Women's Track Oozes with Optimism. Tennis Resorts to Victory. Swimmers Cruise to National Honors. Jumbos [men's Lacrosse] Drop NESCAC [New England Schools and Colleges Athletic Conference] Opener. Tufts 'Soule' Train Derailed. Softball Starts Title Defense With Strong Florida Journey. Baseball Escapes Burden. Tufts Sailing Enjoys View From the Top. [Coach Rich] Beal's The Real Deal.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-04-04; UP055.024.024.00051 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Author [Bette Bao Lord] To Give Commencement Address. Forum Cuts to Chase on Race. Tufts Loses [Katie] O'Dair to MIT Post. Campus Mourns Death of Joseph Lambert. ELBO [Elections Board] Groups To Play More Active Role in Bringing Higher Voter Turnout. Bald Truth From Cafeteria Cashier [Tom Peterson]. Engineering Systems With a Human Heart. Centennial festivities Marred by surprise resignation of [Dr. Leonard] Carmichael. Campuslink Attempts to Build Better Connection. Feminism on the Hill. Search Continues for [Elizabeth] Ammons Replacement. Peace and Justice Department Sponsors Day without violence. Conference tomorrow to discuss contemporary China. Famine exhibition Commemorates Ireland's Great Famine. Tufts Democrats Sponsor Voter Registration drive. Music faculty to learn how to teach with computers. Technology Option Expanded for Liberal Arts Students. High hopes and Hillbillies [sailing]. Women's Track Happy, Healthy. Hollywood Style [Matt] Greenhawt Endures Adversity, Succeeds [men's track]. Lord Jeffs Hands Tufts First [men's tennis] Loss. Men's Lacrosse Bags Babson. Baseball Squirms Past BC [Boston College]. Armed and Dangerous [softball]. Women's Lacrosse Unveils Black Magic on NESCAC [New England Schools and Colleges Athletic Conference].
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-04-11; UP055.024.024.00052 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Faculty Votes Change in Registration, Add Policies. Reverend Jesse Jackson To Preach Race Message at Spring Lecture. Jesse Jackson Versus Bette Bao Lord. Senate Report Stirs Debate Among Faculty. Religion Department Yet to Hire Additional Faculty. Senate Honors Times Publisher [Arthur] Sulzberger Jr. Professor [Alva Couch] Not Just 'Couch' Potato. Making a difficulty decision a Bit Easier. Glum attitudes Prevalent in Year of Cheer. Torn Ticket to Spin Comedic Tale of Love [She Loves Me]. Still Can't Crack Mighty Mystique [Softball] It was a Dark and Stormy...[Swim] Meet. Bates Turns Tufts [Men's] Tennis Inside out. Streak Ends For Women's Lacrosse. S'no Go for the Jumbos [Baseball]. Women's Crew Loses Shirts. [Matt] Lyman Pitches In--At Bat. Tufts Men's Track Ready and Willing. Sailors Put On Fine Show at Friis. Stick Figures [Men's and Women's Lacrosse].
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-04-18; UP055.024.024.00053 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Foul Weather Postpones [Jesse] Jackson Lecture. Vacancies Remain After TCU [Tufts Community Union] Election. Tufts Alum [Kevin Thurm] Contending for Top Spot in Clinton Campaign. Town Hall Meeting Produces suggestions for Tufts Improvement. Senate Does not Slacken at the Final Meeting. EPIIC [Education for Public Inquiry International Citizenship] Focus: Religion, Politics and Society. What to Expect for your 120,000 Education. A See-Saw Battle Baseball Squad Rebounds After Bowing to Ephs. Tennis Engineers 6-1 Victory over MIT. Men's Track Falls Just Short. Trying Times For Women's Track. First Year Crew Coach Seeks More Strength. What? A Tie? Wheaton, Darkness Get Best of Softball Squad. [Troy] Cooper to Carry Olympic Torch. [Sailing Coach Ken] Legler Can't Get No Satisfaction. Women's Lacrosse Regroups. Spring of Hope Fading Fast [Men's Lacrosse.]
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-04-25; UP055.024.024.00054 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. NEMC [New England Medical Center] Seeks Merger to Alleviate Financial Trouble. What does That Guy Do, Anyway? A Day in the Life of University President DiBiaggio. [Andi] Friedman Defeats [Bryan] Krause in TCU [Tufts Community Union] Presidential Race. Antiquated Classrooms Slight Educational Opportunities. Classroom, Court Home to [ Professor James] Watson. New Fraternity [Alpha Phi Delta] Joins Existing Nine on Hill. 1995-1996: The Year's Campus Awakenings. Campus Race Relations, Israeli Tragedies Among Eye Openers. Editor-in-Chief Fondly Reflects on Semester Atop The Observer--"It's Good to Be King". [Doug] Gentile Checks In [Baseball]. Golf Ties FOr 11th at States. [Men's] Lacrosse Gains Morale. Life in a Bubble [Softball] Pressure Cooker [Softball]. Men's Tennis Weathers Tight Schedule. Smart Business Pays For Sailors. Women's Track: 'Our Best Day of the Year'. Crew: Not Big Enough. Men's Track Repeats De-feat. Baseball Makes Half Dozen Errors in 8-5 Loss to Suffolk. Women's Lacrosse A Four-midable Foe.
  - Tufts Observer, 1995-10-26; UP055.024.024.00055 (Box 24)
    [Administration 1995-1996] Faculty fuming over Greeks.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-02-08; UP055.024.024.00056 (Box 24)
    [Agranovsky, Mark] Math professor Todd Quinto divides time between students, research, and community.
  - Tufts Observer, 1995-10-11; UP055.024.024.00057 (Box 24)
    [Allocations Board] C & E chair, members elected, p. 1, 2.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-08-29; UP055.024.024.00058 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Curtis Will Be site of Dining Services' New Coffeehouse. Class of 2000 Ushers in Hew Millennium at Matriculation. Student Activities Office Reshuffles. Great Expectations Abound at Tisch Library. Tufts opts to Give UNICCO [University Cleaning Company] Third Year. Grand Opening Showcases Changes. [Jean] Herbert Helps Ease First Year Fears. First Sounds of Fall Echo A Cappella Tune. Construction Projects Continue Across Campus. Task Force Created To Study Racial Issues on Campus. The Surprising Spring Season Skinny [Men's Tennis]. Spring [Sports] Stars Shine Bright on Hill. New [baseball] Team, Old Results--Success. Former Jumbos still on Hill [Damon Adams, Mike Daily.]
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-09-05; UP055.024.024.00059 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Guster, Rippopotamus To Headline Fall Fest. [Unidentified] Senior Pays for Final Exam Scam. First Net Registration Deemed Success. Good Vibes from Tilton Hall Residents Leave All past Skepticism in the Dust. Ambitious TCU [Tufts Community Union] President [Andi Friedman] Takes Charge. Looking Ahead to Preserve the Memories. Campus Groups Work Together for Voter Registration. Police Reach Out to Ensure Students' safety. Youthful Senate Prepares for Challenges of Inexperience. IM [Intramural] Gym "Almost Ready". The View From the Top [Sailing].
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-09-12; UP055.024.024.00060 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Former U.S. Secretary [James] Baker To Speak. TCU [Tufts Community Union] Treasurer Replcement Voted Into Office. The Trouble With Jumbo Animal Rights Activists Question Morality of Elephant Exhibition. Undergrad [Dara Wolbrom] Dies in Summer Tragedy. Students, Senators Banking on [Lee] Brenner. AIDS Outreach Offers Tools for Healing. Tufts Program in Chile Opens Doors.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-09-26; UP055.024.024.00061 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Burma Group's Appeals Rejected. New Trustee Reps Elected. EPIIC [Education for Public Inquiry and Internatioanl Citizenship] Explores Democracy. Takeout Rejuvinates Hodgdon. Computer Store Crashes. Trading Bratwurst in For Burgers [Mario Langenscheid]. Artsy Craftsy Home for Hot Chocolate. CampusLink at Tufts Connect Get Connected With Students. Volleyball Shocks Ephs for Third Straight Win. Men's Cross Country Gets Running Start. Smooth Sailing So Far for Jumbos. Men's Soccer Back in Business. Busman's Holiday Brings Big-Time Writers to Tufts [Football]. On a Roll! [Women's Soccer]. Football Drops Opener. Field Hockey Still on Track for NCAA [National Collegiate Athletic Association] Revenge. A Rising Star [Cindy Manning].
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-09-19; UP055.024.024.00062 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Wren [Dormitory] Pipes Burst. Respected Professor [Denis Trout] Loses Bid for Tenure. Activists Demand University Boycott of Pepsico Products. Hillel Enters Prime With Its New Center. Passionate Music Maker [P. George Mathews] Takes Baton. Student Volunteers Lend Sympathetic Ears. Culture Respresentative Revote. Williams [football] Again Leads In NESCAC [New England Schools and Colleges Athletic Conference] Title Race. Henry Morgan: Finding Fame. For Jumbos [football] Growing up was hard to do. Ready to Rumble [Football]. [Coach Bill] Samko Hopes Youth Comes of Age. Symposium Announced. Weekend Roundup [sports scores].
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-10-03; UP055.024.024.00063 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. New Minor Links Arts, Engineering. Rookie Senators Retreat. Elections Board Chairs Aims For Improvement. State of the Art Engineering Center to Open in Spring '97. A Campus Commingled. Plato Nietzsche and Robert Devigne. Bahai Builds on Interfaith Contact. Women's Soccer Loses its Star. Volleyball Gets Big Lift From Small [Angela Yost]. Tennis 'Fried' Providence, Heat. Smooth Running for Harriers [Men's Cross Country]. Sailors Up to Old Tricks. Golf on Upswing. [Coach Bill] Samko Wins Recruiting Game. Morrill Victory [filed hockey]. Football Finally Finds its Form. Men's Soccer Picks Up Burst of Speed. Crew Teams to Tufts Media: Drop Dead.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-10-10; UP055.024.024.00064 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Three Degrees, Eight Years Engineering, Med Schools Team Up For New Program. Coming Out on Quad TLGBC [Tufts Lesbian Gay Bisexual Community] Speakers Decry Homophobia at Annual Rally. Completing the Cycle Purchasing Department Pilots Recycled-Product Buying Program. Trustee Rep Elected. Attacks Hit Nerve on the Hill. Sports Forum Draws Pro Team Owners. She's Not your Ordinary Bookworm [Jo-Ann Michalak]. Visions of Tibet Looks to its Future at Tufts. Not So Great Expectations. Tennis Team Battles Injuries, Absences. Mixed Results for Cross Country. Field Hockey Tries to Regain Winning Feeling. Women's Soccer Starts New Streak. Sailing Team Full Of Surprises. [Johnny] Pesky, [Gino] Capelletti To Get Honors. Reality Check! [Football] Shutout Streak Finally Ends [Men's Soccer]. [Katie] Kulmer Leads Off.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-10-17; UP055.024.024.00065 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. University Cracks Down on Party Scene. Sowing Seeds For Green Hill. Dedication [Tisch Library Opening Ceremony]. Media Experts Speak at Forum. From the Hill to Capital Hill? [Jonathan] Raymond Starts the Climb. No Tusk, No Prob: Tufts' Own Jumbo [Ellyn Haikin, Jumbos Mascot]. A Turkish Delight for New Student Group. DiBiaggio's Salary ranked highest in the Northeast. University President [John DiBiaggio] Addresses TCU [Tufts Community Union] Senators, Other Students. Faulty Underground Wiring Leads to Campus Wide Power Failure. Humble Roots of Tisch Family. Men's Cross Country Finishes Strong, Second. Crew Teams Set for Head of the Charles. Tennis still Hoping for Breakthrough. Field Hockey in Home Stretch. Men's Soccer Rolling Towards Showdown. Volleyball Wins Second Straight. There's no place like Home 73rd Homecoming Features Several Key Matchups. Football Getting Closer. A Shooting 'Starr' [Women's Soccer, Jen Starrett]. [Chris] Dimsey, Jumbos Edged Out in 'Shifty' Finish [Sailing].
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-10-24; UP055.024.024.00066 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. PAA [Pan African Alliance] Pushes Higher Black Enrollment. Administration Halts Note-Selling Service. NYNEX [telecommunications] Imposter Defrauds Campus. Architecture Professor Leads Effort for a Beige Ballou. Don't Drink the Water? This Mighty Casey [Coakley- Kopec] Never Strikes Out. Queen's Head Serves Up Literary AntiPasto. Weekend Floods Damage Art at Museum School. Men's Soccer Rebounds With Mediocre Win. [Staci] Arnovitz Leads With Deeds, Not Words. Volleyball Thinking NCAAs. Men Race to Ninth in Nation. Wind, Williams Ruin Homecoming [Field Hockey]. Football's Sold effort Falls Short. Women's Soccer Edged Out in OT. Sailors Struggle in Wet Weekend.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-11-07; UP055.024.024.00067 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Trustees Approve [Denis] Trout Tenure. Race Task Force Defines Mission. Blown Away Election Night Forum Attracts Enthusiastic Crowd. Where Do We Go From Here? TBAG [Tufts Burma Action Group] Regroups after Setbacks. Bringing Together a Community [Pan African Alliance.] Marching to the Beat of a Jumbo Drummer. Missed Chances Cost Football. [Greg] Altman Crowned Scholar King [Football]. Volleyball Victorious Over Wellesley in Five Set Thriller. Sailing Team Dropped to No. 6 in National Poll. Women's Soccer Wins in First Round. Men's Soccer Playing the Waiting Game. Men's Cross Country Best in Tufts' History. [Amy] Hurwitz Comes Through in OT [Field Hockey]. Women's [Cross Country] Team Finishes 10th in ECAC [Eastern College Athletic Conference] Meet.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-11-14; UP055.024.024.00068 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. A Weekend of Jumbo Proportions [Field Hockey]. Field Hockey Wins ECAC [Eastern College Athletic Conference]. Fletcher Hosts High Ranking Military Officials at Conference. Mideast Politics Topic of AIPAC [American Israel Public Affairs Committee] Conference. Bayit Flood Displaces 1 Person. Soccer Senator [Swimmy Minami] Has Eyes on the Ball. Sarabande: Lacing up their dancing Shoes. Senate Pushes Through Safety Resolution in Wake of Attacks on the Hill. Chronicle of Higher Education Notes Tufts' Antiquated Buildings. Women's X-Country Seventh at Regionals. Football Closes Season With Sixth Straight Loss. ECAC Division III Champions [Women's Soccer]. Three Teams NCAA Bound: Volleyball Wins NESCAC [New England Schools and Colleges Athletic Conference] Tourney to Get NCAA [National Collegiate Athletic Association] Bid. Men's Cross Country Earns First Trip to Nationals. Men's Soccer Second Seed in Region.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-11-21; UP055.024.024.00069 (Box 24)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Cracker, Guster Play the Pub. TUPD [Tufts University Police Department] Rolls With Punches. FBI Raids Office of College Cult. Oxfam Collective, Cafe Strive to Make World Hunger Personal. No Sweet 16 for Annual Knable Feast. Health Services Director [Michelle Bowdlar] Sets Goals For New Office. Green is Keen for Professor [George] Ellmore. Building a Bridge to the 21st Century. Men's Cross Country Finishes a Lucky Seventh. Volleyball Bumped from NCAAs Breaks Don't go Soccer's Way. Sailors Bounce Back to Second.
- Tufts Observer, 1996 -- 2000; UP055.025; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of loose copies of the Tufts Observer newspaper, dated from December 5, 1996 to March 4, 1999. In 1969, the Observer replaced the Tufts Weekly as the weekly student-published paper. The Observer states that its objective is to be 'the newspaper of record' for Tufts University. The Observer covers current events and university news and sports. Typical features include editorials and opinion pieces, a calendar of events, art and culture articles, creative works, and comics.
  - Tufts Observer, 1996-12-05; UP055.025.025.00001 (Box 25)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Congressman Joe Kennedy Addresses Cabot Crowd. B&G Res. Life Respond to Dorm Decay. Latest Assault Spurs Police Forum. Curtis Hall Coffeehouse To Open Doors Next Semester. Library Extends Late Night Study Trial Period. Sophomore [Jayme Novotny] Death Stuns Community. Activism on Both Sides of Pacific. Student Groups Prepare for Holiday Season. After Busy Semester Senate Evaluates Success. Queen of Big O [Observer] Revels in Finale, Goes out Cheering, "All for One, and Headlines for All". [Men's] Swimmers Post Big Wins at Clark. Women [swimming] Pull Even and Look Forward. Men's [squash] Team Sees Fifth Loss in a Row. Women's Basketball Blown Away in Last Two Games. [Men's] B-Ball Wins Defense. [Ice] Hockey Romps Suffolk, Then Suffers First Loss.
  - Tufts Observer, 1997-01-23; UP055.025.025.00002 (Box 25)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Library Expands Electronic Holdings. Tufts Alum [Bill Richardson] Appointed to U.N. Post. NE Medical Center OKs Merger. Litter Here For Keeps, Says B&G. Good to the Last Drop [Brown and Brew]. Apple a Day Not enough for [Michelle] Bowdler. ASA [Arab Student Association] Brings Taste of Middle East to Tufts. TCU [Tufts Community Union] Senators Set Goals For the Coming Semester. Men's Squash Set for Matches with Bates and Bowdoin. Women's Track Team Drops Last Two Meets. Men's Track Competes in Quad Cup. Women's Squash Takes Five of Six Matches at Williams on Sunday. Women's B-Ball Breaks Six Game Losing streak. Men's Swimming Coasts to Win at MIT. Hockey gets Win Over Suffolk. Men's Basketball to Meet Powerhouse Salem State Tonight. Women's Swimming Back from Barbados.
  - Tufts Observer, 1997-01-30; UP055.025.025.00003 (Box 25)